reshareable.tv 2015-05-19

# Privacy Policy | Re Shareable TVRe Shareable TV

ReShareable.tv’s Privacy Policy

On ReShareable.tv, privacy issues are a high priority for us and we follow standard industry practices to maintain your personal information. We respect your privacy and are committed to the same.

Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

**1\. Privacy Policy Coverage**  
ReShareable.tv’s Privacy Policy covers treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you are on the ReShareable.tv site.

**2\. Information collected by ReShareable.tv**  
ReShareable.tv collects personally identifiable information when during registration, ReShareable.tv asks for your name and email address. Once you have sent us this information and sign in to our services you are not anonymous to us anymore.

**3\. Use of information by ReShareable.tv**  
ReShareable.tv uses information collected for two purposes:

(a) Information provided to us is used to customize the advertising and content you see and to inform you about special offers, new products and other services which are offered completely free of cost. ReShareable.tv will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties. Unless it is specifically stated otherwise. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than ReShareable.tv, you will be notified prior to the data collection or transfer. 

(b) ReShareable.tv may disclose personally identifiable information about you to third parties when:

  * we have your consent to share the information
  * we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested and given your consent
  * we have to cooperate with the investigations for unlawful activities

**4\. Collection of Information by Third Parties**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org.

**5\. Updation of personal information**  
Members can edit their ReShareable.tv User Account Information and ReShareable.tv profile by sending an email Member’s ReShareable.tv account can be deleted or deactivated, but doing so will result in not being able to access any members-only area of the iIoveIndia network But the residual information will remain in our archive records. ReShareable.tv can change this policy any time.

Our members are our assets and we will never knowingly do anything to harm this trust. Any information given voluntarily to us by you is used to enhance your experience on our site, to provide you with interactive or personalized elements on the sites and to better prepare for future content based on your areas of interests. We gather this information to determine which areas are liked by our site members and which are not liked based on the traffic to those areas.

We don’t track what individual members read, but rather try to determine how well each page performs. This helps us continue to provide better services to you. We also use the information that is gathered to tailor the content to best suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our members.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

---
